There are also questions about access to digital media
as a rehabilitation opportunity for the inmates.
It's a way for me to approach the digital imperative.
By looking at environments that may be perceived as non-digital.
There I can clearly see change processes that apply to society at large.
Another project, which is linked to the library environment and digitalisation,
is about automated decision -making in the public sector.
Automation in the public sector where you delegate different decisions
to algorithms and technological infrastructure.
I am conducting interviews with people working in the public sector.
Specifically, I interview people at the Employment Service at different levels.